let questions11 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "abnormal",
      answer: "B. unnormal",
      options: [
        "A. seltsam",
        "B. unnormal",
        "C. gewöhnlich",
        "D. üblich"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "bamboo",
      answer: "A. Bambus",
      options: [
        "A. Bambus",
        "B. Schilf",
        "C. Rohr",
        "D. Gras"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "blossom",
      answer: "C. Blüte",
      options: [
        "A. Knospe",
        "B. Pflanze",
        "C. Blüte",
        "D. Zweig"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "compass",
      answer: "D. Kompass",
      options: [
        "A. Karte",
        "B. Uhr",
        "C. Navigation",
        "D. Kompass"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dialect",
      answer: "B. Dialekt",
      options: [
        "A. Sprache",
        "B. Dialekt",
        "C. Akzent",
        "D. Aussprache"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "dishonest",
      answer: "A. unehrlich",
      options: [
        "A. unehrlich",
        "B. falsch",
        "C. inkorrekt",
        "D. täuschend"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "dwarf",
      answer: "C. Zwerg",
      options: [
        "A. Gnom",
        "B. Kobold",
        "C. Zwerg",
        "D. Elf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "ecosystem",
      answer: "B. Ökosystem",
      options: [
        "A. Umwelt",
        "B. Ökosystem",
        "C. Naturraum",
        "D. Biotop"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "fatal",
      answer: "D. tödlich",
      options: [
        "A. gefährlich",
        "B. schlimm",
        "C. ernst",
        "D. tödlich"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "impatient",
      answer: "C. ungeduldig",
      options: [
        "A. nervös",
        "B. hastig",
        "C. ungeduldig",
        "D. rastlos"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "leaf",
      answer: "A. Blatt",
      options: [
        "A. Blatt",
        "B. Laub",
        "C. Zweig",
        "D. Ast"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "manuscript",
      answer: "B. Manuskript",
      options: [
        "A. Dokument",
        "B. Manuskript",
        "C. Schrift",
        "D. Text"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "marsh",
      answer: "D. Sumpf",
      options: [
        "A. Moor",
        "B. Teich",
        "C. See",
        "D. Sumpf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "patience",
      answer: "A. Geduld",
      options: [
        "A. Geduld",
        "B. Ausdauer",
        "C. Ruhe",
        "D. Beständigkeit"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "perfume",
      answer: "C. Parfüm",
      options: [
        "A. Duft",
        "B. Aroma",
        "C. Parfüm",
        "D. Essenz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "pond",
      answer: "B. Teich",
      options: [
        "A. See",
        "B. Teich",
        "C. Tümpel",
        "D. Pfütze"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "proverb",
      answer: "D. Sprichwort",
      options: [
        "A. Redensart",
        "B. Spruch",
        "C. Weisheit",
        "D. Sprichwort"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "pursuit",
      answer: "C. Verfolgung",
      options: [
        "A. Jagen",
        "B. Nachlauf",
        "C. Verfolgung",
        "D. Nachgehen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to recite",
      answer: "A. vortragen",
      options: [
        "A. vortragen",
        "B. sprechen",
        "C. aufsagen",
        "D. rezitieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wilderness",
      answer: "B. Wildnis",
      options: [
        "A. Wüste",
        "B. Wildnis",
        "C. Wald",
        "D. Natur"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions11;